Guide to the Religious Education Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Board and Committee Records, Series II
  - Board of Directors: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Board of Directors: Minutes, correspondence, 1981 Jan (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Board of Directors, 1981 Nov (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Board of Directors, 1982 May (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Board of Directors, 1982 Jul-Nov (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Executive Committee, 1929-1932 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Executive Committee, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Executive Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Executive Committee, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Executive Committee, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Executive Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Executive Committee, 1949-1951 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Executive Committee, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Executive Committee, 1954-1959 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Executive Committee, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Executive Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Executive Committee, 1971 Jan-Mar (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Executive Committee, 1971 Apr (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Executive Committee, 1971 May-Jun (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Executive Committee, 1971 Jul-Aug (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Executive Committee, 1971 Sep (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Executive Committee, 1971 Dec (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Executive Committee, 1972 Mar-Apr (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Executive Committee, 1972 Jun-Sep (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Executive Committee, 1972 Dec (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Executive Committee, 1974 Jan-Mar (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Executive Committee, 1974 Jun-Nov (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Executive Committee, 1975 Jan-Mar (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Executive Committee, 1975 Jun-Nov (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Executive Committee, 1976 Jan (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Executive Committee, 1976 Mar-Nov (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Executive Committee, 1977 Jan-Jun (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Executive Committee, 1977 Sep (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Executive Committee, 1978 Jan-Apr (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Executive Committee, 1978 May-Nov (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Executive Committee, 1979 Jan-Mar (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Executive Committee, 1979 Jun-Sep (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Executive Committee, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Executive Committee, 1981 Jan-Mar (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Executive Committee, 1981 Jun-Oct (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-1983 Mar (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Nominating Committee, 1916-1925 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Nominating Committee, 1941-1944, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Nominating Committee, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Nominating Committee, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 155-156)
  - Nominating Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 157)
  - Nominating Committee, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - Editorial Committee, 1928,1931-1932 May (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - Editorial Committee, 1932 Oct-1933 (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - Editorial Committee, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 161)
  - Editorial Committee, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - Editorial Committee, 1631935 (Box 12, Folder 164)
  - Editorial Committee, 1940-1948 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - Editorial Committee, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - Editorial Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 167)
  - Editorial Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Editorial Committee, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Editorial Committee, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - Editorial Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - Editorial Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - Editorial Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - Editorial Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 174)
  - Editorial Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 175)
  - Editorial Committee: Questionnaire responses, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 176-178)
  - Advisory Committee on Doctoral Abstracts in Religious Education, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 179)
  - Advisory Committee on Doctoral Abstracts in Religious Education, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 180)
  - Advisory Committee, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 181)
  - Committee on Relationships, 1930, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 182)
  - Program Committee, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - Program Committee, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - Special Committee on Program and Policy, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 185)
  - Program Committee, 1936-1939 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - Membership Committee, 1939-1942, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - Program Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - Central Planning Committee, 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - Commission on Higher Education, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 190)
  - Central Planning Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 191)
  - Planning Committee for the Observance of the 50th Anniversary of the R.E.A., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - Committee on Philosophy of Education of the R.E.A., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - Development Committee, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 194)
  - Committee on Some Functions of the R.E.A. in Dealing with Moral and Spiritual Values in Public Schools, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 195)
  - Search Committee for General Secretary Minutes/communications of Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 196)
  - Individuals recommended to Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 197-198)
  - Candidates considered - C, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - Candidates considered - H-K (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - Candidates considered - M (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - Candidates considered - N-S (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Committee on Nature and Functions of the R.E.A., 1970 Mar-Jun (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Committee on Nature and Functions of the R.E.A., 1970 Sep-Dec (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - Task Force on the Support of Professional Religious Educators, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Central Planning Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - Task Force on the Support of the Professional Religious Educator, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Future of the International Convention of the R.E.A., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - Special Committee on Future Meetings of the R.E.A., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - Central Planning Committee, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 210)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Nature and Purpose of the R.E.A., 1981 Mar-Apr (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Nature and Purpose of the R.E.A., 1981 Aug-Oct (Box 15, Folder 212)
- Secretarial Files, Series III
  - Pre-Wornom Era (1906-1952)
    - Prominent correspondents
      - George A. Coe, Mark May, Adelaide Case, Harrison Elliott, Henry Cope, 1922-1923 (Box 16, Folder 213)
      - George A. Coe to T.G. Soares, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 214)
      - Richard C. Hall, Harrison Elliott, J.M. Artman, William Adams Brown, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 215)
      - Harrison Elliott, J.M. Artman, William C. Bower, Adelaide Case, George A. Coe, Hugh Hartshorne, 1931-1932 (Box 16, Folder 216)
      - William C. Bower, J.M. Artman, Harrison Elliott, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 217)
      - Hugh Hartshorne, Harrison Elliott, E.W. Blakeman, E.J. Chave, Stewart G. Cole, Adelaide Case, George A. Coe, 1935-1937 (Box 16, Folder 218)
      - Hugh Hartshorne, E.J. Chave, Harrison Elliott, J.M. Artman, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 219)
      - E.J. Chave, Herbert L. Seamans, Harrison Elliott, 1939-1940 (Box 16, Folder 220)
      - Harrison Elliott, George A. Coe, E.J. Chave, Hugh Hartshorne, Stewart Cole, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 221)
      - Harrison Elliott, George A. Coe, Herman Wornom, F. Ernest Johnson, 1942-1947 (Box 16, Folder 222)
      - E.J. Chave, F. Ernest Johnson, Harrison Elliott, Sophia L. Fahs, S.P. Franklin, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 223)
      - S.P. Franklin, E.J. Chave, L. Stidley, Harrison Elliott, Ernest Kuebler, E.W. Blakeman, 1949 Jan-Mar (Box 16, Folder 224)
      - L. Stidley, Harrison Elliott, Ernest Kuebler, Hugh Hartshorne, S.P. Franklin, E.J. Chave, 1949 Apr-May (Box 16, Folder 225)
      - S.P. Franklin, S. Stidley, Harrison Elliott, 1949 Jun-Oct (Box 16, Folder 226)
      - L. Stidley, S.P. Franklin, E.J. Chave, Ernest Kuebler, Stewart Cole, E.W. Blakeman, Harrison Elliott, 1949 Nov-Dec (Box 16, Folder 227)
      - L. Stidley, E.J. Chave, Harrison Elliott, Willard Uphaus, S.P. Franklin, Ernest Kuebler, 1950 Jan-Mar (Box 16, Folder 228)
      - L. Stidley, Stewart Cole, Lawrence Little, E.J. Chave, S.P. Franklin, Harrison Elliott, 1950 Apr-Sep (Box 17, Folder 229)
      - L. Little, L. Stidley, Harrison Elliott, S.P. Franklin, E.J. Chave, 1950 Oct-Dec (Box 17, Folder 230)
      - S.P. Franklin, Harrison Elliott, E.J. Chave, Israel Chipkin, Cleveland E. Dodge, 1951 Jan-Jul (Box 17, Folder 231-232)
      - L. Stidley, L. Little, S.P. Franklin, H. Wornom, I. Chipkin, E. Kuebler, 1951 Aug-Dec, n.m. (Box 17, Folder 233)
      - S.P. Franklin, L. Stidley, L. Little, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 234)
    - Topical Files
      - Coe, George A. (Box 17, Folder 235)
      - Fahs, Sophia Lyon (Box 17, Folder 236)
      - Hartshorne, Hugh (Box 17, Folder 237)
      - International Council of Religious Education (Box 17, Folder 238)
      - Northwestern University Religious Education program (Box 17, Folder 239)
      - University of Chicago - Religious Education program (Box 17, Folder 240)
  - Wornom Era (1952-1970)
    - General files
      - A (Box 18, Folder 241)
      - Academy of Religion and Mental Health (Box 18, Folder 242)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 18, Folder 243)
      - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education (Box 18, Folder 244)
      - American Association for Jewish Education (Box 18, Folder 245)
      - American Association of Theological Schools (Box 18, Folder 246)
      - Association for Coordination of University Religious Affairs (Box 18, Folder 247)
      - Association of Professional Religious Educators (Box 18, Folder 248)
      - B (Box 18, Folder 249)
      - Bronson, Oswald (Box 18, Folder 250)
      - C (Box 18, Folder 251)
      - Center for Applied Research in the Apostolate (Box 18, Folder 252)
      - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions (Box 18, Folder 253)
      - Character Research Project, Union College (Box 18, Folder 254)
      - Chronicle Guidance Publication (Box 18, Folder 255)
      - Cline, Victor B. (Box 18, Folder 256)
      - Cody, John Cardinal (Box 19, Folder 257)
      - Commission on the Study of the Place of Religion in State Universities (see also: Series VIII) (Box 19, Folder 258)
      - Coordinating Committee on Religious Education for the Handicapped (Box 19, Folder 259-263)
      - D (Box 19, Folder 264)
      - Educational Testing Service (Box 19, Folder 265)
      - Encyclopedias (Box 19, Folder 265)
      - F (Box 19, Folder 266)
      - Fallaw, Wesner (Box 19, Folder 267)
      - Fahs, Sophia Lyon (Box 19, Folder 268)
      - G (Box 19, Folder 269)
      - Garbutt, Glenn (Box 19, Folder 270)
      - H (Box 20, Folder 271)
      - Internal Revenue Service (Box 20, Folder 272)
      - J (Box 20, Folder 273)
      - K (Box 20, Folder 274)
      - L (Box 20, Folder 275)
      - Little, Lawrence C. (Box 20, Folder 276)
      - Losoncy, Lawrence (Box 20, Folder 277)
      - M (Box 20, Folder 278)
      - McLeod, James C. (Box 20, Folder 279)
      - Maves, Paul B. (Box 20, Folder 280)
      - Mayer, Otto (Box 20, Folder 281)
      - Mid-Atlantic Professors of Religious Education (Box 20, Folder 282)
      - Miller, Randolph C. (Box 21, Folder 283)
      - N (Box 21, Folder 284)
      - NCCC - Christian Education and Ecumenism (Box 21, Folder 285-286)
      - NCCC - Professional and Research Section (Box 21, Folder 287)
      - P (Box 21, Folder 288)
      - Panoch, James V. (Box 21, Folder 289)
      - Philosophy of Education Society (Box 21, Folder 290)
      - Q (Box 21, Folder 291)
      - R (Box 21, Folder 292)
      - S (Box 21, Folder 293)
      - Smith, Richard U. (Box 21, Folder 294)
      - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary (Box 22, Folder 295)
      - Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary (Box 22, Folder 295)
      - Spiro, Jack D. (Box 22, Folder 295)
      - T (Box 22, Folder 296)
      - Troyer, Maurice E. (Box 22, Folder 297)
      - Turner, Eugene (Box 22, Folder 298)
      - United Methodist "The Future of Religious Education" (Box 22, Folder 299)
      - Vieth, Paul (Box 22, Folder 300)
      - W (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - Topical files
      - Anti-Vietnam War activities (Box 22, Folder 302)
      - Birth control (Box 22, Folder 303)
      - Catholic education (Box 22, Folder 304)
      - Catholic-Jewish relations (Box 22, Folder 305)
      - Comic books (Box 22, Folder 306)
      - Juvenile delinquency (Box 23, Folder 307)
      - Mass media (Box 23, Folder 308-310)
      - Moral and spiritual values in California Junior Colleges (Box 23, Folder 311)
      - Notes - miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 312-313)
      - Religion in Higher Education (see also: Series VIII) (Box 24, Folder 314)
      - Religion in Public Education (Box 24, Folder 314A)
      - Research projects in Human Social Behavior at Harvard University (Box 24, Folder 315)
      - Visits in Boston and Cambridge (1962) (Box 25, Folder 316)
      - Miscellaneous research reports, papers (Box 25, Folder 316A)
  - Kathan Era (1970-1982)
    - General files
      - A (Box 26, Folder 317)
      - Adult Education Association (Box 26, Folder 318)
      - American Jewish Committee (Box 26, Folder 319)
      - Ansley, Dorothy (Box 26, Folder 320)
      - Association for Religious Education - England (Box 26, Folder 321)
      - B (Box 26, Folder 322)
      - Baxter, Edna (Box 26, Folder 323)
      - Bower, William Clayton (Box 26, Folder 324)
      - C (Box 26, Folder 325)
      - Catholic Education (Box 26, Folder 326)
      - Character Research Project (Box 26, Folder 326)
      - Christian Education Center - Dubuque, Iowa (Box 26, Folder 327)
      - Christian Educators Fellowship (Box 26, Folder 328)
      - Community of Religious Education Directors (CORED) (Box 26, Folder 329-331)
      - Confraternity of Christian Doctrine (CCD) (Box 26, Folder 332)
      - Council on the Study of Religion (Box 26, Folder 332-333)
      - Cully, Iris and Kendig (Box 27, Folder 334)
      - D (Box 27, Folder 335)
      - Drinan, Father Robert (Box 27, Folder 336)
      - E (Box 27, Folder 337)
      - Educational Communication Association - Consultation on Religion in the Public Schools (Box 134, Folder 1538)
      - F (Box 27, Folder 338)
      - Fahs, Sophia Lyon (Box 27, Folder 339)
      - Fowler, James W. (Box 27, Folder 340)
      - Fuchs-Kreimer, Nancy (Box 27, Folder 341)
      - G (Box 27, Folder 342)
      - Goldman, Ronald (Box 27, Folder 343)
      - H (Box 27, Folder 344)
      - Heschel, Abraham (Box 27, Folder 345)
      - Hofinger, Johannes (Box 27, Folder 345)
      - Horowitz, Harve C. (Box 27, Folder 346 -347)
      - Inter-faith Religious Education Week - Richmond, Virginia (1973-1974) (Box 27, Folder 348)
      - J (Box 27, Folder 349)
      - Jesus Christ Superstar (Box 27, Folder 349)
      - Journal of Current Social Issues (Box 134, Folder 1586)
      - K (Box 28, Folder 350)
      - Kaplan, Klive (Box 28, Folder 350)
      - Koulomzin, Sophie (Box 28, Folder 350)
      - L (Box 28, Folder 351)
      - Lee, J.M.; Lefroy-Owen, Peter (Box 28, Folder 352)
      - Ligon, Ernest M. (Box 28, Folder 353)
      - M (Box 28, Folder 354)
      - Miller, Randolph C. (Box 28, Folder 355-358)
      - N (Box 28, Folder 359)
      - National Catechetical Directory (Box 28, Folder 360)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 28, Folder 360)
      - National Consultation on Religion and Public Education (Box 134, Folder 1587)
      - National Council on Religion and Public Education (see: additional material in YDL RG 34) (Box 134, Folder 1588)
      - National Council on Religion and Public Education (Box 134, Folder 1589)
      - National Council on Religion and Public Education (Box 134, Folder 1590)
      - National Council on Religion and Public Education (Box 134, Folder 1591)
      - National Council on Religion and Public Education (Box 134, Folder 1592)
      - National Council on Religion and Public Education (Box 14, Folder 1593)
      - National Council for the Churches of Christ (Box 28, Folder 361)
      - National Council for Jewish Education (Box 28, Folder 362)
      - National Inventory of Parish Catechetical Programs (Box 28, Folder 363)
      - O (Box 28, Folder 364)
      - Olson, Bernhard (Box 28, Folder 365)
      - Olson, Bernhard (Box 29, Folder 366)
      - P (Box 29, Folder 367)
      - Peatling, John (Box 29, Folder 368-370)
      - Placement service (Box 29, Folder 371)
      - Price, J.M. (Box 29, Folder 372)
      - Public Education Religion Studies Center (Box 134, Folder 1594)
      - Questionnaire re. teaching of religions and ethics in Connecticut schools (Box 134, Folder 1595)
      - R (Box 29, Folder 373)
      - R.E.A. brochure (Box 29, Folder 374)
      - Religious Education Week (1972-1976) (Box 29, Folder 375)
      - Religious Instruction Association (Box 29, Folder 376)
      - Religion-Social Studies Curriculum Project (Box 29, Folder 377)
      - Sa - Soc (Box 29, Folder 378)
      - Sou - Sy (Box 29, Folder 379)
      - Schmidt, Stephen (Box 29, Folder 380-382)
      - Simon, Sidney B. (Box 30, Folder 383)
      - Southern Baptist R.E.A. (Box 30, Folder 384-385)
      - Stokes, Ken (Box 30, Folder 386-388)
      - T (Box 30, Folder 389)
      - Time Consultants (Box 30, Folder 390)
      - United Ministries in Public Education (Box 134, Folder 1596)
      - United States Catholic Conference (Box 30, Folder 391)
      - V (Box 30, Folder 392)
      - Vieth, Paul H. (Box 30, Folder 393)
      - W (Box 30, Folder 394)
      - Westerhoff, John (Box 30, Folder 395-396)
      - Westerhoff, John (Box 31, Folder 397)
      - White House Conference on Children (Box 134, Folder 1597)
      - Wornom Festschrift (Box 31, Folder 398-404)
      - Yale Divinity School (Box 31, Folder 405)
      - First names only (Box 31, Folder 406)
    - Writings by Kathan
      - "Religious Education in the '70's: Human Liberation in an Uptight Age" (1970) (Box 32, Folder 407)
      - "Patriotism, Piety and Pedagogy: Confronting Civil Religion" in Religion Teacher's Journal (1975 Dec) (Box 32, Folder 408)
      - "Civil Religion in America - A Bibliography (1975) (Box 32, Folder 409)
      - Biographical essay re. Randolph Crump Miller (1977) (Box 32, Folder 410)
      - "New Interest in the Bible: The Contexts of Bible Study Today" (c.1979) (Box 32, Folder 411)
      - "Religious Education and Public Policy" (1979) (Box 32, Folder 412)
      - Unidentified notes (Box 32, Folder 413)
- Meetings, Series IV
  - National R.E.A. Meetings
    - Pre-1953
      - 41st Annual Convention: Chicago, 1903 (Box 33, Folder 414)
      - 2nd: Philadelphia, 1904 (Box 33, Folder 414)
      - 3rd: Boston, 1905 (Box 33, Folder 414)
      - 4th: Rochester, 1907 (Box 33, Folder 414)
      - 5th: Washington, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - 6th: Chicago, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - 8th: Providence, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - 9th: St Louis, 1912 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - 11th: New Haven, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - 12th: Buffalo, 1915 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - 14th: Boston, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - 15th: New York (specialized conference on "Community Organization"), 1918 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - 17th: Pittsburgh, 1920 (Box 33, Folder 416)
      - 23rd: Toronto, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 416)
      - 25th: Philadelphia, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 416)
      - Des Moines, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 416)
      - 29th: New York, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 416)
      - Cincinnati, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 417)
      - Detroit, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 418-419)
      - Rochester ("Annual meeting"), 1935 (Box 33, Folder 420)
      - Pittsburgh ("Annual meeting"), 1936 (Box 33, Folder 421)
      - Columbus, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 422)
      - Unidentified location, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 423)
      - New York ("Biennial Convention"), 1950 (Box 33, Folder 424)
    - 50th Anniversary- 1953 Convention
      - Leadership lists Attendance/Sponsors, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 427)
      - Leadership - services performed by (Box 34, Folder 428)
      - Leadership Correspondence: A - F (Box 34, Folder 429)
      - Leadership Correspondence: G - L (Box 34, Folder 430)
      - Leadership Correspondence: M - Z (Box 34, Folder 431)
      - Attendance/Sponsors: Miscellaneous lists and mailings (Box 34, Folder 432)
      - Attendance/Sponsors: Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 34, Folder 433)
      - Sponsors: A-P (Box 34, Folder 434)
      - Sponsors: P-Z, miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 435)
      - Corresponding Members (Box 35, Folder 436)
      - Regional Attendance: Middle Atlantic, New England, National, Pennsylvania (Box 35, Folder 437)
      - Regional Attendance: Mountain Pacific: Southern/South Central, North Central, Canada (Box 35, Folder 438)
      - Planning: Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 439)
      - Planning: Notes (Box 35, Folder 440)
      - Planning: Committee records (Box 35, Folder 441)
      - Planning: Lodging (Box 35, Folder 442)
      - Planning: Printed Matter (Box 35, Folder 443)
      - Planning: Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 36, Folder 444-445)
      - Program (Box 36, Folder 446-447)
      - Seminar reports (Box 36, Folder 448-449)
      - Finance/Administration (Box 36, Folder 450)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 37, Folder 451-454)
      - Re. endorsements (Box 37, Folder 455)
      - Religious News Service (Box 37, Folder 456)
      - Commendations (Box 37, Folder 457)
    - 1957 Convention
      - Planning (Box 38, Folder 458-461)
      - Program (Box 38, Folder 462-466)
      - Finance (Box 38, Folder 467)
      - Leadership (Box 39, Folder 468-472)
      - Attendance (Box 39, Folder 473-474)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 39, Folder 475-479)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 40, Folder 480-489)
    - 1962 Convention
      - Planning (Box 41, Folder 490-495)
      - Program (Box 41, Folder 496-497)
      - Leadership (Box 42, Folder 498-505)
      - Leadership (Box 43, Folder 506-509)
      - Attendance (Box 43, Folder 510-512)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 44, Folder 513-520)
    - 1966 Convention
      - Planning (Box 45, Folder 521-523)
      - Program (Box 45, Folder 524-531)
      - Program (Box 46, Folder 532-535)
      - Leaders (Box 46, Folder 536-539)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 46, Folder 540)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 47, Folder 541-544)
    - 1969 Convention
      - Planning (Box 48, Folder 545-551)
      - Program (Box 48, Folder 552-554)
      - Attendance (Box 49, Folder 555)
      - Leadership (Box 49, Folder 556-561)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 49, Folder 562-564)
    - 1972 Convention
      - Planning (Box 50, Folder 565-566)
      - Program (Box 50, Folder 567-570)
      - Leadership (Box 50, Folder 571-574)
      - Leadership (Box 51, Folder 575-578)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 51, Folder 579-580)
    - 1973 Convention
      - Planning (Box 51, Folder 581-582)
      - Program (Box 51, Folder 583-584)
      - Leadership (Box 52, Folder 585-589)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 52, Folder 590)
    - 1975 Convention
      - Planning (Box 53, Folder 591-594)
      - Program (Box 53, Folder 595-598)
      - Leadership (Box 53, Folder 599)
      - Leadership (Box 54, Folder 600-601)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 54, Folder 602-604)
    - 1977 Convention
      - Planning (Box 55, Folder 605-607)
      - Program (Box 55, Folder 608-611)
      - Leadership (Box 55, Folder 612-613)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 55, Folder 614)
    - 1979 Convention
      - Planning (Box 56, Folder 615-618)
      - Program (Box 56, Folder 619-622)